<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Intentionally Bilingual - raising kids the non-native way! on Nimke.nl</title><link>https://intentionally-bilingual.github.io/hugosite/</link><description>Recent content in Intentionally Bilingual - raising kids the non-native way! on Nimke.nl</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://intentionally-bilingual.github.io/hugosite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Stage of linguistic differentiation (2;6-5 years)</title><link>https://intentionally-bilingual.github.io/hugosite/bilingualism/language-development/differentiation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://intentionally-bilingual.github.io/hugosite/bilingualism/language-development/differentiation/</guid><description>In this post I will talk about the stage of linguistic differentiation. This stage starts around the age of 2;6 years and lasts until the age of 5 years. In this stage the children’s social and cognitive skills improve massively, alongside the so called language explosion they seem to acquire. Everything goes fast and is learned fast, before you know it the child is 4 or 5 years old and no longer talking in that telegraphic style, but speaks in well versed sentences which are even fully intelligible!</description></item><item><title>stage of linguistic completion (5+ years)</title><link>https://intentionally-bilingual.github.io/hugosite/bilingualism/language-development/5+/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://intentionally-bilingual.github.io/hugosite/bilingualism/language-development/5+/</guid><description>Language development of children ago 5 and up</description></item><item><title>stage of linguistic completion (28+ years)</title><link>https://intentionally-bilingual.github.io/hugosite/bilingualism/language-development/28+/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://intentionally-bilingual.github.io/hugosite/bilingualism/language-development/28+/</guid><description>Let hope my husband learn a language other then javascript and python.
Ad dolor ad qui pariatur minim cillum velit incididunt tempor dolor. Proident proident occaecat non Lorem ex minim. Enim aliquip qui aliqua nostrud proident irure aute. Minim officia elit proident ea. Culpa elit ut do veniam exercitation mollit ex dolore aliquip enim occaecat consectetur anim nisi. Aute minim dolor Lorem eu.
Exercitation culpa ut Lorem nisi. Minim do amet cupidatat in duis culpa ad.</description></item></channel></rss>